hey everyone this is Nick at bobbin.com
and today we're talking about the best
fat banners for women if you want to see
the full written version of this video
you can just Google it with bar Bend
plus best women's fat burners and also
if you decide you want to purchase any
of these products we've got links to
them to buy in the description below so
let's get started with number one oh
actually one more thing before we start
uh this does not constitute medical
advice I'm not a doctor that kind of
stuff is important to say for these
sorts of products make sure if you are
trying to lose weight that you speak to
your doctor before you embark on any new
supplement or weight loss regimen all
right starting off with the best women's
fat burner overall we looked at a ton of
them lean Bean is our top pick contains
12 ingredients that could potentially
help to move you closer to your weight
loss goals a big part of the appeal here
is glucomannan that's like a thickener
that is made from the root of the
Japanese konjac plant so it's like very
very fibrous and there's a few
interesting studies that have suggested
that it could help to reduce appetite
because it expands in your stomach it's
a really cool ingredient you don't see
very often but it also includes other
fat burning ingredients like cayenne
pepper green tea extract black pepper
extract which could help to increase the
absorption of all these ingredients here
according to a 2016 paper from the
proceedings of the National Academy of
the Sciences of the United States of
America this is also an all-natural
supplement and it also happens to be
vegetarian friendly like the capsules
aren't made of animal gelatin or
anything it's not technically caffeine
free there's like a little bit of
caffeine left over from some of the
green coffee bean extract but you're
only going to get about 10 milligrams
out of this which is like about a tenth
of a cup of coffee so that over the
course of the day most people wouldn't
really consider much of a stimulant so
you can call it stem free if you like
all right the best thermogenic fat
burner for women we're gonna go with
jacked factories burn XT so this is a
thermogenic fat burner containing
cayenne pepper extract it's about 50
milligrams per dose which can help to
like increase the amount of calories you
burn in a given day by raising your
body's internal temperature a bit in
addition this product contains
L-Carnitine green tea extract and
caffeine which can all also help with
fat burn the black pepper extract here
as in lean Bean can help you to better
absorb the ingredients like make it more
effective in that regard the smoke does
contain a relatively high dose of
caffeine though it's 270 milligrams per
dose which is about the amount you're
getting like one and a half big cups of
Starbucks coffees so while this amount
isn't harmful it might be tricky if you
have like sensitivities to caffeine so
next up is the best women's fat burner
for women over 40 and you know what I'm
gonna go with lean Bean again because
you know not that much changes or over
40. I mean I do I understand that like
the older we get the amount of calories
we burn in a day can decrease which
would mean that it can be harder to lose
fat also like our hormones can change a
little bit as we age and so on so I
wouldn't say there are no changes after
40. we're talking about fat burners
largely the same principles apply
appetite depression is key and also
increasing the amount calories you've
been in the day I eat them at Genesis
and also increasing fat oxidation these
all play a role lean Bean helps with all
three of these areas especially the
glucose Manon as I mentioned so whatever
your age I would say lean Bean is the
best fat burner the only thing that I
would mention though is because of that
glucomannan which is like a fiber that
expands in your stomach it does suck up
a lot of water because it expands so
you're supposed to take a good two
glasses of water maybe more every time
you have a dose of lean beans so just
keep plenty of water around but you know
that'll encourage you to drink more
water next up is the best fat burner for
belly fat we really like burn lab Pro
for this one it contains ingredients
that can help your body to retain muscle
while eliminating fat gtf chromium is a
part of this it might help with your
body choose more glucose for energy
instead of storing it as fat burn lead
Pro also contains cayenne pepper extract
which may help to increase your body's
temperature like increase your
metabolism the amount of calories you
burn as well and on top of that burn lab
includes hmb an ingredient you don't use
usually find in fat babies and that can
potentially help you to build and retain
muscle while losing fat it is worth
noting that burn lab Pro is stimulant
free as well which for some might be a
plus for early morning gym goers you
know they might appreciate a cup of
coffee with this as well
now the best natural fat burner for
women is Legion Phoenix fat burner this
one's 100 natural and stimulant free as
well if you get the student-free version
anyway with no artificial sweeteners or
food dyes or unwanted fillers you can be
assured this is like a high quality
all-natural blend Legion is also one of
the most transparent brands on the
market so they make sure that they list
exactly what's in their products and how
much of it is listed as well there are a
lot of companies with like proprietary
Blends that are much less transparent
and Legion also lists all these studies
behind the ingredients on their website
ingredients here include Thai ginseng
5-HTP and Forskolin all of which may
potentially help to burn fat suppress
appetite and regulate the metabolism and
also it has to add a dose of B vitamins
which you won't find in many fat burners
and is linked to efficient energy usage
the best pre-workout fat burner is going
to be transparent Labs lean so this
isn't technically marketed as a fat
burner it's marketed as a pre-workout
with like fat burning qualities but like
for our purposes here it's a really good
pre-workout fat burner it contains all
like a lot of pre-workout ingredients
like citrulline malate and beta alanine
Branch chain amino acids but it also
includes L-Carnitine which can help to
turn fat into energy caffeine we can
also do something similar and also ciner
friend which has some interesting links
to increase the amount of calories you
burn in a day like thermogenesis a happy
bonus is that there are no artificial
flavors or sweeteners or preservatives
it's just like noting this is powdered
so if you're someone who prefers to have
pills you can carry around with you
throughout the day that's going to be
quite the right product here but that's
something you can mix into a drink and
have before you work out this is a good
and surprisingly tasty option the best
research fact fat burner for women
meanwhile is transparent labs this is a
company that really does homework the
fat burner has a lot of egcg and
antioxidant in green tea that could
increase calorie burn the stinging and
tyrosine for Focus there's Forskolin and
sinephrine which could help with
thermogenesis like increasing the amount
of calories you burn now if appetite
suppression is what you want to
emphasize this is not quite as effective
as saline beans this is still a really
really effective fat burning product
it's really well researched has a lot of
really interesting studies linked on the
product page and if you don't like the
caffeine they've also got a stim free
version as well so there's something for
everyone with this one so what about the
best value women's fat burner well for
that one we're going to go with Jack
Factory's burn XT because this is a very
simple formula in some respects like
there are just five ingredients here
which helps keep the cost down the
effectiveness is still very high for
example this contains cayenne pepper
extract which can play a key role in
increasing thermogenesis like increasing
amount of calories that you burn it's
got caffeine as well which is also great
for people who want to well take this in
the morning before a workout for example
plus it could help to increase fat
oxidation as well there's also black
pepper extract that can help with
absorption and that might be a perk to a
lot of people unless of course you're
allergic to it and there's also a couple
other ingredients here that are
important as well like L-Carnitine and
green tea leaf extract so just those
five degrees helps keep the cost
relatively low again relative to the
industry but still they're all pretty
effective and effectively dosed all
right the best women's fat burner for
appetite suppression though is gonna be
lean Bean this doesn't have plenty of
ingredients that could potentially help
to increase thermogenesis and fat
oxidation but the real benefit here is
in the appetite suppression as I
mentioned earlier this contains a pretty
good dose we'll have a very good dose
effect of glucomannan which is made from
the root of the Japanese konjac plant
what it does is that's the type of fiber
that expands in the belly and is really
effective According to some research at
decreasing appetite because you know it
takes up room in your stomach so that's
the reason why I'm a big fan of lean
mean for appetite suppression we've had
some other ingredients some other
products on this list of fat burners
that have some really interesting
dosages of fat oxidation thermogenesis
but if appetite is what you're really
struggling with and appetite is Far and
Away the most important aspect of weight
loss and fat loss because it helps you
to you know eat less food definitely I
will go with leaving here just make sure
you drink plenty of water throughout the
day because it can suck up a lot of
fluid in your belly and make you kind of
thirsty so you know make sure you keep
your water and take High lastly we've
got the best fat burner for women's
bodybuilding maintaining a caloric
deficit for fat loss for an extended
period of time can be really tough for
female and male bodybuilders and it can
also lead to muscle loss as well so for
women who are specifically training to
gain or retain muscle with a minimum fat
gain and maximum fat loss this formula
from Burn lab Pro could be helpful at
helping you to achieve your goals so
burn lab Pro both about as clean and
science-backed ingredient label and for
good reason the formula includes fat
burning ingredients that have been shown
in a lot of research to help to work in
Fat Loss such as capsaicin and black
pepper extract they also include a trace
mineral called gtf chromium which is
supposed to help to coax your body into
using more glucose for energy instead of
storing it as fat but what really makes
this formula like pretty muscle friendly
is use of hmb or hydroxy methyl butyrate
which is a chemical that is broken down
from the amino acid leucine there's one
double-blind placebo-controlled study
that showed that Combat Sports athletes
who took hnb for 12 weeks showed
significant body composition
improvements meaning they lost fat and
either retained or gained muscle mass
all right that about does it for our
list of the best women's fat burners if
you want to see the written version of
this video so you can go through it at
your own pace let me check out some of
the studies we've been talking about you
can find that if you just Google bar
Bend plus best women's fat burners if
you decide you want to purchase any of
these you've got links in description
below as well and lastly make sure you
subscribe here as well to Barbara's
YouTube channel because we've got a ton
of videos on the latest news and reviews
purchasing guides exercise guides and
everything else coming up
foreign